export default {
  id: 'jp_word_ms_conjunction_1_1_2',
  name: '일어달 접속연어연체 LV1-1 (19자 / 글자)',
  data: [
    { question: '/그러나, 하지만', answer: ['が'] },
    { question: '/하지만, 그러나', answer: ['けれども'] },
    { question: '/그러나', answer: ['しかし'] },
    { question: '/그러자', answer: ['すると'] },
    { question: '/그래서', answer: ['そこで'] },
    { question: '/그리고', answer: ['そして'] },
    { question: '/그리고, 또한, 게다가', answer: ['かつ'] },
    { question: '/그리고 나서', answer: ['それから'] },
    { question: '/그래서', answer: ['それで'] },
    { question: '/그러면', answer: ['それでは'] },
    { question: '/그렇지 않으면', answer: ['それとも'] },
    { question: '/게다가', answer: ['それに'] },
    { question: '/따라서, 그러니까', answer: ['だから'] },
    { question: '/그럼', answer: ['では'] },
    { question: '/하지만', answer: ['でも'] },
    { question: '/그러나', answer: ['ところが'] },
    { question: '/그런데, 그건 그렇고', answer: ['ところで'] },
    { question: '/또, 게다가', answer: ['また'] },
    { question: '/또는, 혹은', answer: ['または'] }
  ]
}
